Contact

7132915438 (Mobile) donp@glasscraft.net

www.linkedin.com/in/ donaldpolansky (LinkedIn) www.temporal-investigations.com/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Strategic Planning
Operations Management
Manufacturing

Donald Polansky

Customer Service Manager & CRM Administrator at GlassCraft Door Company

Houston, Texas

Summary

Experienced Customer Relationship Management Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the building materials industry. Skilled in Operations Management, Retail, Pricing Strategy, Team Building, and Manufacturing. Strong business development professional with experience in both customer and data side analytics.

Experience

GlassCraft Door Company Customer Service Manager June 2014 - Present

GlassCraft Door Company CRM Manager March 2012 - Present

Customer relationship management (CRM) is a model for managing a company's interactions with current and future customers. It involves using technology to organize, automate, and synchronize sales, marketing, customer service, and technical support.

The CRM Administrator is charged with setting up and maintaining all aspects of the CRM system from processes, procedures, customizations, and automations.

GlassCraft has deployed the Microsoft Dynamics CRM 2011 since early 2012.

GlassCraft Door Company
Production Control Manager
February 2006 - June 2014 (8 years 5 months)

Oversee the coordination of project order completion from order entry to shipping. Maintain the ever changing flow of production and the time restriction shifts in each department. Liason between Customer Service & Production to ensure open lines of communication internally as to better communicate

with our outside clients. Member of the company's Senior Management Team (SMT)

Steves & Sons

Quality Management Representative September 2004 - December 2005 (1 year 4 months)

Instituted ISO 9001:2000 program from inception to initial certification.

Responsible for company compliance and structure relating to procedural and process development.

H. E. Butt Co.

C-COM - SA Region

July 1997 - August 2004 (7 years 2 months)

Operations management for the logisitc and customer oriented workings of the stores layout and effeciency.

Education

The University of Texas at San Antonio Criminal Justice/Theology (2000 - 2002)